<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Performance Investigator Setup for Remote Profiling">

<intro>
<description>
Follow these steps to enable and start remote profiling on a target device. 
To open a related help page for more specific information, click the question mark icon at the end of the task title row.
</description>
</intro>

<item
      dialog="true"
      skip="false"
      title="Install Nokia PC Suite on the PC.">
<description>
Install the latest <b>Nokia PC Suite</b> on your PC and launch Carbide.c++ IDE.
</description>
</item>



<item
      dialog="true"
      skip="false"
      title="Connect a USB cable.">
<description>
Connect a USB cable to the PC and then to the target device.
</description>
</item>
<item
      title="Start the Performance Investigator Import Wizard">
   <description>
      Start the Import Wizard in Carbide.c++ by selecting <b>Carbide &gt; Performance Investigator</b>
   </description>
</item>
<item
      href="/com.nokia.carbide.cpp.pi.doc.user/html/tasks/analyser/collect_prof_data_remotely.htm#First"
      title="Import data from device by tracing">
   <description>
      On the <b>Select Profiler Data Files</b> page, select to get profiler data <b>From Device via TraceViewer</b>.
   </description>
</item>



<item title="Check connection settings" dialog="true" skip="false" href="/com.nokia.traceviewer.help/html/reference/preferencesconnection.htm">
<description>
Before you start tracing, check the connections settings. Select <b>Connection settings</b> to open the TraceViewer Connections Setting dialog.
After checking and saving the connection settings, click <b>Refresh Plug-ins List</b>. If the connection to the target device is working correctly, a list of the available plug-ins appears.
</description>
</item>

<item
      dialog="true"
      href="/com.nokia.carbide.cpp.pi.doc.user/html/tasks/analyser/collect_prof_data_remotely.htm#Select"
      skip="false"
      title="Set plug-ins for tracing and prefix for created file.">
<description>
Select the plug-ins you want to trace from <b>Select Plug-ins for Tracing list</b>
Enter the file prefix to be used for the trace data file.
</description>
</item>

<item
      dialog="true"
      href="/com.nokia.carbide.cpp.pi.doc.user/html/tasks/analyser/collect_prof_data_remotely.htm#Stop"
      skip="false"
      title="Run the trace.">
<description>
Click <b>Start Tracing</b> to begin and carry out the use case with your application. When you are finished with the use case, click <b>Stop Tracing</b>. A new trace file name appears in the <b>Created Profiler Data Files</b>list.
If you wish you can run another trace. Just enter a new prefix for the second file and change the setting if you wish.
</description>
</item>



<item
      dialog="true"
      href="/com.nokia.carbide.cpp.pi.doc.user/html/tasks/analyser/an_load_trace_files.htm#Select_Known_Available_Information"
      skip="false"
      title="Finish the import">
<description>
Click <b>Next</b> to continue with the import. 
For detailed instructions, click the question mark icon to open the Help.
</description>
</item>

<item title="Open the file for analysis" dialog="true" skip="false" href="/com.nokia.carbide.cpp.pi.doc.user/html/reference/analyzer/PI_view.htm">
<description>
   If you imported only one file, the data will open directly to the PI Analyser view.
 If you imported several files, they will be listed in the PI view and you can double click on an item to view and analyse it in PI Analyzer.
</description>
</item>

</cheatsheet>
