<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="CrashAnalyser Quick Start Guide: Capturing and analysing crash data">
   <intro>
      <description>
         This tutorial gives instructions on how to capture and analyse crashes that occur in the mobile device using the CrashAnalyser Carbide.c++ Extension. 
<br/><br/>
You can obtain crash data in two ways:
<br/>
- by retrieving the files manually and transferring them to the PC
<br/>
- by using TraceViewer to automatically transfer the files. 
<br/><br/>To open a related help page, click the question mark icon at the end of the task title row.
      </description>
   </intro>
<item
         dialog="false"
         skip="true"
         title="(Optional) Obtain the crash files from your device manually">
      <description>
         A mobilecrash file is generated to the root of the memory card or the C: directory.
<br/><br/>
These files are in binary format and need to be moved to your PC and decoded into readable format before you can analyse what caused the crash. 
<br/><br/>
To transfer the files to your PC, you can:  
<br/><br/>
- Use USB or Bluetooth connection.
<br/>
- Send the file as a message from the device by using the FileBrowser tool.
<br/>
- Use a file transfer utility (for example, PC Suite or similar).
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         dialog="false"
         href="/com.nokia.s60tools.crashanalyser.help/html/tasks/enable_auto_crash_logging.htm"
         skip="true"
         title="(Optional) Capture crash data with TraceViewer">
      <description>
         A faster way to capture crash data from the device to the PC is by using traces.
<br/><br/>
To use this option, enable TraceViewer in CrashAnalyser&apos;s Preferences. (It is enabled by default.) 
<br/><br/>
When activated, TraceViewer will automatically &quot;listen&quot; to crashes and transfer the panic codes to the PC.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         href="/com.nokia.s60tools.crashanalyser.help/html/tasks/import_crash_files.htm"
         title="Import the crash files in CrashAnalyser">
      <description>
         To start working on the files on your PC, start the CrashAnalyser wizard from the <b>Carbide &gt; CrashAnalyser</b> menu and import the files for decoding. 
<br/><br/>
<b>Note!</b> It takes time to decode files, so do not select too many files to be decoded at a time.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="View and analyse the crashes" dialog="true" skip="false" href="/com.nokia.s60tools.crashanalyser.help/html/concepts/how_to_analyse_crash.htm">
      <description>
         To start analysing an imported file, double-click it on the CrashAnalyser main view. 
<br/><br/>
The Crash Visualiser contains four different tabs that help you diagnose what caused the crash in the device; what was the reason (for example, Symbian OS panic or exception), and in which process and in which thread the crash occurred.
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
