<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Setting up and using Analyze Tool">
   <intro>
      <description>
         Follow these steps to start analyzing memory leaks. To open a related help page, click the question mark icon at the end of the task title row.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="(Optional) Check the prerequisites" dialog="true" skip="true" href="/com.nokia.s60tools.analyzetool.help/html/gettingstarted/prerequisites.htm">
      <description>
         Check that your workstation contains the necessary components for using AnalyzeTool. Tip! If you obtained AnalyzeTool from the SymSEE installation, you can proceed to the next step.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Define the data gathering mode." dialog="true" skip="false" href="/com.nokia.s60tools.analyzetool.help/html/concepts/preferences.htm">
      <description>
         Go to <b>Preferences</b> to define how to capture the trace data: either by using the out put to trace mode or output to file system mode.
Tip! You can also define the output mode by using the AnalyzeTool toolbar.
      </description>
      <command serialization="org.eclipse.ui.window.preferences(preferencePageId=com.nokia.s60tools.analyzetool.preferences.AnalyzeToolPreferencePage)" confirm="false">
      </command>
   </item>
   <item title="Create a project in Carbide" dialog="true" skip="true" href="/org.eclipse.cdt.doc.user/tasks/cdt_t_proj_new_with_template.htm">
      <description>
         Make sure you have your project created in Carbide.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Build your project with AnalyzeTool" dialog="true" skip="false" href="/com.nokia.s60tools.analyzetool.help/html/tasks/build.htm">
      <description>
         To make memory leak analysis possible, you must build each project with AnalyzeTool. You can activate the project build from the AnalyzeTool toolbar or from the pop-up menu in the Project Explorer. You can also change the output mode from the AnalyzeTool toolbar.
      </description>
      <command serialization="org.eclipse.ui.views.showView(org.eclipse.ui.views.showView.viewId=com.nokia.s60tools.analyzetool.ui.MainView)" confirm="true">
      </command>
   </item>
   <item title="Capture data" dialog="true" skip="false" href="/com.nokia.s60tools.analyzetool.help/html/tasks/capture.htm">
      <description>
         You have two possible choices to capture data.
<br/><br/>
1. If you have selected the <b>Output to trace</b> mode in AnalyzeTool build, AnalyzeTool captures trace data directly from the target hardware. You can start and stop the trace capturing from the AnalyzeTool toolbar. See the <b>TraceViewer help</b> for detailed information on creating a TraceViewer connection.
<br/><br/>
2. If you have selected the <b>Output to file system</b>  mode in AnalyzeTool build, AnalyzeTool collects the test data into a file in the target hardware. You need to transfer this file to a PC after the test run is completed.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="View and analyze memory leaks" dialog="true" skip="false" href="/com.nokia.s60tools.analyzetool.help/html/tasks/viewmemoryleaks.htm">
      <description>
         The memory leak analysis results are displayed in the AnalyzeTool window. Test runs with the memory leak information is displayed in the left pane. The right pane shows the information on the selected memory leak call stack.
<br/><br/>
Test run details will be shown in the AnalyzeTool view automatically after the data capture in Output to trace mode. You can also open the memory analysis data file  later by clicking <b>Open and analyze data file</b> in the AnalyzeTool toolbar.
<br/><br/>
You can define how much detail you want to see in the memory leak analysis report by using the AnalyzeTool toolbar.
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
